[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["South Korean Presidential Office"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Is that your belief it will happen today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "Well, that's the belief of the South Korean Presidential Office.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "What is your question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "I'm a South Korean citizen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "What is the sense you're getting form the people of Seoul?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "It's two-fold.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Seoul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kyung"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Is it any different or do you detect it may be different?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I think for all the reasons that Kyung says, it's different mostly because nobody quite knows how Kim Jong-Un is going to react, and unlike his father and his grandfather, when one of these provocations is ratcheted up, they seemed, according to the U.S., to know how to get off, how to get on the off ramp.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Christiane"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What is your take on the current crisis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, as Christiane said, we -- this is a new leader and we really don't know if he is the power, the main power or who is the power, you know, behind him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Can China do enough, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, apparently the U.S. says no, not enough yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pyongyang", "North Korea"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "When you were on the North side, what is your experience of the North Koreans by comparison to the South Koreans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "EE: Well, if I recall my detention in Pyongyang, I thought North Korea, when you talked to (INAUDIBLE), with their pride intact.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Koreans", "South Koreans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Did you see the weapon he was using?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "You both think that you should be allowed to carry guns at school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "But you do have armed -- you do have armed security guards there, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Where were they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "They are -- they are all throughout the campus, sir, but since there's about I'm guessing around eight of them, if I remember correctly, sir, and there's a couple hundred or thousand students on campus at one time during this, so eight officers can't guard and protect everyone on campus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Let me ask you both, don't you think -- I mean, how old are you both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I'm 22, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "You're not saying everyone should -- how many should have guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "MD", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Anyone that's permitted and goes through the right training, sir, I think should be able to carry a gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Do you agree with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Why would you start the conversation by being so completely facetious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Because actually the way you've been thinking about the whole gun issue, I found just totally out of touch with reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 197, "question": "So how do you equate that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, they -- well, they're probably northeast liberals who don't understand --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "And what do you think about the NRA's argument that the only way to stop a bad guy with a gun is a good guy with a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "It doesn't work.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What is your reaction as to -- senators, to this letter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", ":", "NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "My reaction is the American people are going to be very aghast and deeply angry if a handful, small group of United States senators block a vote.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "But how is this going to happen nationally when there's absolutely zero interest in making this happen from a bunch of cowardly politicians who want to protect their own backyards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, listen, there's zero interest amongst 14 members of the Senate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago", "Texas"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Steve Latourette, where do you sit with all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Tonight I sit in Chicago, and I'm a little nervous based upon what the guy in Texas said, to tell you the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Latourette"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Why shouldn't we know who the hell is selling guns to who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "You're presuming that they are universal background checks that will work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "ONWAY: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "It's better than nothing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "It's a start.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "It's unimportant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Yes, it's unimportant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Latourette"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "-- do you think it would have, if any, if a parent of a child who was killed in Newtown -- what impact, if any, do you think it would have on Congress or America at large?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ":", "WP", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Let me go to Steven Latourette first on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "LOCATION": ["Newtown", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Representatives", "Columbine"], "LOCATION": ["Newtown", "Aurora"]}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Would it change things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I got to tell you, any senator or member of the House of Representatives that isn't very familiar with what happened in Newtown and Columbine and Aurora has been living in a cave some place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Even if the universal background check did lead to some form of database of who owns guns, what the hell's wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I'm just going to venture a couple guesses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What do you think generally of this debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I think that the gentleman that you were just speaking with, he said that people are -- they know what happened and they're in tune to what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Marc, is this just the White House, again misplaying things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "I think it's much adieu about nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Steven Latourette, I mean, am I getting worked up for the wrong reason here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Yeah, you're getting worked up for the wrong reason.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Latourette"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Sure, my question is -- my question is what sort of message does it send when you have people like Beyonce and Jay-Z traveling to Cuba?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "OK, good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"], "LOCATION": ["Cuba"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130409pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Marc?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Again, much adieu about nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]